Finding Aid for Michigan Bell Telephone Company Photographs 1949-1983
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Positive Photographic Prints
  - Employment - Hearing aids
    - Fire departments/fire prevention (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - First aid (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Flint, Mich.-Various jobs (splicers, p.o., c.o., traffic), color transparencies (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Floats (various centennial and other celebrations) (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Flowers (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Food (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Ford World Headquarters (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Foreign telephone operations (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Fort Custer (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Fort Wayne (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Four-H camp (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Frames-C.O. frames, 5 folders (Box 8, Folder 302-306)
    - General Motors (aerial views) (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Gift telephones (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Girl Scouts (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Glee Club, 1941-1965 (scattered dates) (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Good citizens (employees participating in community activities) (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Grosse Isle U.S. Naval Air Base (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Hand set (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Handicapped Training Center (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Hearing aids (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Hobbies - Non-traditional jobs
    - Hobbies, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 316-317)
    - Homemaking (largely cooking) (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - Horizon installation-Dominos Pizza (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Horseback riding (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Hospitals
      - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 321)
      - Percy Jones Hospital, Battle Creek, Michigan, 1948-1952 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Houses-Residential, 1955-1961 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Housing construction (Inkster, Allen Park), 1949-1955 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Huts (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Independent telephone companies (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Inquiring reporter (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Installers, 6 folders (Box 9, Folder 328-333)
    - Instruments
      - Antique (Box 9, Folder 334)
      - Bellboy (Box 9, Folder 335)
      - Call director (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Intercept offices (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Jack and plug (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Junior Achievement, 4 folders (Box 9, Folder 339-342)
    - Kappel, Frederick (AT&T chairman) (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Key cabinets (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Key Telephone Unit (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Legal Department (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Legal-Miscellaneous (litigation photos) (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Libraries and librarians (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Lighthouses (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - Linemen, 3 folders include color transparencies, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 350-352)
    - Lottery (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Lounges (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - Magicall instruments (Box 10, Folder 355)
    - Magnavox (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Magneto sets (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Management, 3 folders (Box 10, Folder 358-360)
    - Manholes (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - "Mark Sense" (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Marketing Department, 5 folders (Box 10, Folder 363-367)
    - Marketing-Directories (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Marketing-Public Telephone (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Medical Group, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 370-371)
    - Message registers (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - Microphones (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Microwave horns (Detroit, Michigan) (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Microwave towers, 3 folders (Box 11, Folder 375-377)
    - Military Communications Autovon (Box 11, Folder 378)
    - "Miss DIG" (Box 11, Folder 379)
    - Missiles-Nike-Hercules (Box 11, Folder 380)
    - Missiles-Nike-Zeus (mainly) (Box 11, Folder 381)
    - Mobile Central Office (Box 11, Folder 382)
    - Mobile radio telephone, 4 folders (Box 11, Folder 383-386)
    - Mobile switchboards (Box 11, Folder 387)
    - Mobile telecoach (Box 11, Folder 388)
    - Models-Professional (Box 11, Folder 389)
    - Motor Vehicles
      - Compact (Box 11, Folder 390)
      - Company trucks, 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 391-392)
      - Maintenance (Box 11, Folder 393)
      - New (Box 11, Folder 394)
      - Old (Box 11, Folder 395)
      - Wrecked (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Museum displays (Box 11, Folder 397)
    - National Guard (Box 11, Folder 398)
    - Network Services (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - Newspapers (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - Night school students (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - Night workers (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Non-traditional jobs (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Northern District - Red Cross
    - Northern District (employee activities; Grand Marais Exchange, etc.) (Box 12, Folder 404)
    - Northland Shopping Center (Box 12, Folder 405)
    - Office-Michigan Bell president's office, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 406)
    - Office workers-Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 407)
    - Open Houses
      - Detroit-Trinity (Box 12, Folder 408)
      - Flint (Box 12, Folder 409)
      - Frankenmuth (Box 12, Folder 410)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 12, Folder 411)
      - Lansing (Box 12, Folder 412)
      - Pontiac (Box 12, Folder 413)
      - Port Huron (Box 12, Folder 414)
      - Redford (Box 12, Folder 415)
      - Roseville (Box 12, Folder 416)
      - Royal Oak (Box 12, Folder 417)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 12, Folder 418)
      - Wayne (Box 12, Folder 419)
      - Webster (Box 12, Folder 420)
    - Operator Services-TOPS offices (Box 12, Folder 421)
    - Operators, 13 folders (Box 12, Folder 422-434)
    - Outside companies (photos of other firms), 3 folders (Box 12, Folder 435-437)
    - Paintings
      - Robert Thom Michigan history series, 23 folders (Box 13, Folder 438-460)
        (arranged alphabetically by title of painting; each folder contains color transparencies, negatives, and color print)
      - Robert Thom (artist working on Michigan history series; with F. Clever Bald; exhibits of paintings) (Box 13, Folder 461)
    - Panel Phones (Box 13, Folder 462)
    - Parades (Box 13, Folder 463)
    - Pay Stations
      - General, 9 folders (Box 13, Folder 464-472)
      - Coinless (Box 13, Folder 473)
    - People (various business and personal activities), 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 474-475)
    - Personalities (employee activities and hobbies), 6 folders (Box 14, Folder 476-481)
    - Personnel relations (Box 14, Folder 482)
    - Phone Center Store (Box 14, Folder 483)
    - Picture Phone (Box 14, Folder 484)
    - Plant training (lab set ups for plant school), 3 folders (Box 14, Folder 485-487)
    - Pole hole digger (Box 14, Folder 488)
    - Police officers (Box 14, Folder 489)
    - Police-Michigan State Police (Box 14, Folder 490)
    - Political figures/political events (includes JFK arrival in Detroit, 1962) (Box 14, Folder 491)
    - Power (diesel and turbine) (Box 14, Folder 492)
    - Pre-wiring (telephone planned homes) (Box 14, Folder 493)
    - Printing shop and various printing activities (Box 14, Folder 494)
    - Prison-State Prison at Jackson (Box 14, Folder 495)
    - PBX Dimension (Box 14, Folder 496)
    - PBX (operators, equipment, staff activities), 3 folders (Box 15, Folder 497-499)
    - PBX (use by other companies; include work operations of various firms, 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 500-501)
    - Posters, 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 502-503)
    - Princess Phones, 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 504-505)
    - Public offices (commercial offices and employees), 6 folders (Box 15, Folder 506-511)
    - Public Relations (include Michigan Bell photographers) (Box 15, Folder 512)
    - Radar (Box 15, Folder 513)
    - Radio Relay Stations (Box 15, Folder 514)
    - Radio Telephone Hour (Box 15, Folder 515)
    - Radio Telephone Overseas (Box 15, Folder 516)
    - Radioisotopes (Box 15, Folder 517)
    - Rapcon Relay Rack (Box 15, Folder 518)
    - Rate Case (Box 15, Folder 519)
    - Rebate Project (Box 15, Folder 520)
    - Recording (Box 15, Folder 521)
    - Red Cross (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Repairmen - Stores
    - Repairmen (Box 16, Folder 523)
    - Repeater (Box 16, Folder 524)
    - Retired people, 2 folders (Box 16, Folder 525-526)
    - Ringing Machines (Box 16, Folder 527)
    - Riot (Detroit) restorations, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 528)
    - Rural, 3 folders (Box 16, Folder 529-531)
    - Safety
      - General, 3 folders (Box 16, Folder 532-534)
      - Driving (Box 16, Folder 535)
      - Home (Box 16, Folder 536)
      - Hunting (Box 16, Folder 537)
      - "On the Job" (Box 16, Folder 538)
      - Skiing (Box 16, Folder 539)
      - Water (Box 16, Folder 540)
    - Salute to Women Who Work (Box 16, Folder 541)
    - Sanders Bakery (Box 16, Folder 542)
    - Santa Claus story (Box 16, Folder 543)
    - Satellite-Telstar (Box 16, Folder 544)
    - Scenic views
      - Canada (mainly border areas) (Box 16, Folder 545)
      - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 16, Folder 546-547)
      - United States (Box 16, Folder 548)
    - Schools
      - General (Box 16, Folder 549)
      - Drop Out (Box 16, Folder 550)
      - Home to School Telephone (Box 16, Folder 551)
    - Seasons-Four seasons (mainly winter) (Box 17, Folder 552)
    - Secretaries (mail room) (Box 17, Folder 553)
    - Security (Box 17, Folder 554)
    - Selfridge Air Force Base (Box 17, Folder 555)
    - Service Action Force (Box 17, Folder 556)
    - Service emblems (Box 17, Folder 557)
    - Service representatives, 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 558-559)
    - Servicemen (Box 17, Folder 560)
    - Ship to shore telephone (Box 17, Folder 561)
    - Signs, 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 562-563)
    - Solar batteries (Box 17, Folder 564)
    - Speaker Phones (Box 17, Folder 565)
    - Special equipment (Box 17, Folder 566)
    - Special events
      - Alexander Graham Bell centennial celebrations (Box 17, Folder 567)
      - Auto Show (Box 17, Folder 568)
      - Cadillac (Mich.)-75th anniversary (Box 17, Folder 569)
      - Constitutional Convention (Box 17, Folder 570)
      - Detroit Golden Jubilee, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 571)
      - Detroit (1,000,000 phone) (Box 17, Folder 572)
      - Flint (100,000 phone) (Box 17, Folder 573)
      - Grand Rapids (100,000 phone; include views of the city, Grand Rapids Furniture Museum) (Box 17, Folder 574)
      - Ispeming centennial (Box 17, Folder 575)
      - Marquette centennial (Box 17, Folder 576)
      - Michigan (2,000,000 phone) (Box 17, Folder 577)
      - Michigan (3,000,000 phone) (Box 17, Folder 578)
      - Michigan State University centennial (Box 17, Folder 579)
      - Michigan Week (Box 17, Folder 580)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 581)
      - Port Huron centennial (Box 17, Folder 582)
      - Royal Oak (50th anniversary of business office; also 100th anniversary of the city) (Box 18, Folder 583)
      - Salk polio vaccine announcement, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 584)
      - Telephone (50,000,000 phone) (Box 18, Folder 585)
      - Telephone Ice Show (Box 18, Folder 586)
      - Traverse City (Cherry Festival) (Box 18, Folder 587)
      - Wayne (centennial) (Box 18, Folder 588)
      - Wyandotte centennial (Box 18, Folder 589)
      - Your Voice is You program (Box 18, Folder 590)
    - Special Services Issue (Box 18, Folder 591)
    - Splicers (Box 18, Folder 592)
    - Sports
      - Baseball, 3 folders (Box 18, Folder 593-595)
      - Baseball (Detroit Tigers) (Box 18, Folder 596)
      - Basketball (Box 18, Folder 597)
      - Bowling (Box 18, Folder 598)
      - Curling (Box 18, Folder 599)
      - Fishing (Box 18, Folder 600)
      - Football (Box 18, Folder 601)
      - Golf (Box 18, Folder 602)
      - Hockey (Box 18, Folder 603)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 604)
      - Racquetball (Box 18, Folder 605)
      - Sailing (also boating) (Box 18, Folder 606)
      - Skiing (Box 18, Folder 607)
      - Soapbox Derby (Box 18, Folder 608)
      - Swimming (Box 18, Folder 609)
      - Table Tennis (Box 18, Folder 610)
      - Tennis (Box 18, Folder 611)
      - Volleyball (Box 18, Folder 612)
    - Stockholders (Box 18, Folder 613)
    - Stocks and bonds, 2 folders (Box 18, Folder 614-615)
    - Stores (Box 18, Folder 616)
  - Strikes - Wurtsmith
    - Strikes
      - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 617)
      - 1954 (Box 19, Folder 618)
      - (includes negatives), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 619)
      - 1974 (Box 19, Folder 620)
      - Labor demonstration(?); parade (?) (Box 19, Folder 621)
    - Students
      - Elementary (also colleges and university) (Box 19, Folder 622)
      - Foreign (Box 19, Folder 623)
      - High School Cooperative (Box 19, Folder 624)
      - Telephone training (Box 19, Folder 625)
      - Telezonia (Box 19, Folder 626)
    - Suggestion (employee) plan and winners, 4 folders (Box 19, Folder 627-630)
    - Surveys (Box 19, Folder 631)
    - Switchboards
      - General (Box 19, Folder 632)
      - Mobile and marine (Box 19, Folder 633)
      - PBX (Box 19, Folder 634)
    - Switching systems (Box 19, Folder 635)
    - Switchmen (Box 19, Folder 636)
    - Switchroom helpers (Box 19, Folder 637)
    - Tax-excise (Box 19, Folder 638)
    - Taxes-State Property Tax (Box 19, Folder 639)
    - Teachers working with company (Box 19, Folder 640)
    - Telephone bills (Box 19, Folder 641)
    - Telephone Hour, 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 642-643)
    - Telephone poles (Box 19, Folder 644)
    - Telephone-Radio telephone (Box 19, Folder 645)
    - Telephone usage
      - Basements and patios (Box 19, Folder 646)
      - Bedrooms, 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 647-648)
      - Den (Box 20, Folder 649)
      - Farm Interphone (Box 20, Folder 650)
      - Home Interphone (Box 20, Folder 651)
      - Kitchens, 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 652-653)
      - Living room (Box 20, Folder 654)
      - Office (also outside companies) (Box 20, Folder 655)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 656)
    - Teleprinter-Dec II (Box 20, Folder 657)
    - Teletypewriters, 3 folders (Box 20, Folder 658-660)
    - Television
      - General, 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 661-662)
      - Antennas, 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 663-664)
      - Bell System, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 665)
      - Commercials (Box 20, Folder 666)
      - Educational (Box 20, Folder 667)
      - Expressway (Box 20, Folder 668)
      - Perchville (Box 20, Folder 669)
      - Television Shows (Box 20, Folder 670)
      - Television Stations (Box 20, Folder 671)
      - WWJ-TV (Box 20, Folder 672)
    - Terminals (terminal shelters) (Box 20, Folder 673)
    - Test Centers (Box 20, Folder 674)
    - Tie Lines
      - 1976, 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 675-676)
      - 1977 (Box 20, Folder 677)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 678-679)
    - Time Service (Box 20, Folder 680)
    - Toll dialing equipment (Box 21, Folder 681)
    - Tools (Box 21, Folder 682)
    - Touch-A-Matic Phone (Box 21, Folder 683)
    - Touchtone (Box 21, Folder 684)
    - Tours
      - General (Box 21, Folder 685)
      - Bell Building (Box 21, Folder 686)
      - Bell System (Box 21, Folder 687)
    - Towers-CATV (Box 21, Folder 688)
    - Town Meeting (Box 21, Folder 689)
    - Traffic Department-Staff activities (Box 21, Folder 690)
    - Traffic Service Position System (Box 21, Folder 691)
    - Traffic Signals (Box 21, Folder 692)
    - Trailers (Box 21, Folder 693)
    - Training
      - General, 3 folders (Box 21, Folder 694-696)
      - Telephone manners (Box 21, Folder 697)
    - Transaction Phone (Box 21, Folder 698)
    - Transformer & Absorption Machine (Box 21, Folder 699)
    - Transistors (Box 21, Folder 700)
    - Transportation Story (different modes of getting to work) (Box 21, Folder 701)
    - Travel Bureau (Box 21, Folder 702)
    - Treasury Department (Box 21, Folder 703)
    - Tree trimming (Box 21, Folder 704)
    - Trimline, 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 705-706)
    - Turkish engineers (Box 21, Folder 707)
    - Typists (Box 21, Folder 708)
    - Uniforms (Box 21, Folder 709)
    - Union contract negotiations (Box 21, Folder 710)
    - United Foundations, 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 711-712)
    - Upbeat, 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 713-714)
    - USO Center (Box 21, Folder 715)
    - Vacations/vacation sites (Box 22, Folder 716)
    - Vail Medal, 4 folders (Box 22, Folder 717-720)
    - Ventilation equipment-Bell Building (Box 22, Folder 721)
    - Visible Speech Machine (Box 22, Folder 722)
    - Wages (Box 22, Folder 723)
    - Weather Services (Box 22, Folder 724)
    - Weddings (Box 22, Folder 725)
    - Western Electric, 3 folders (Box 22, Folder 726-728)
    - Western Electric repair (Box 22, Folder 729)
    - Wires (Box 22, Folder 730)
    - Women's Club, 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 731-732)
    - Word Processing Center (Box 22, Folder 733)
    - Wurtsmith Air Force Base (Box 22, Folder 734)
- Photographic Negatives
  The Photographic Negatives series dates from 1949 to 1983. It consist mainly of 4 x 5 and 5 x 7 negatives until 1975 when the company shifted over to 35 mm negative strips. Up to 1953, this series was arranged by a consecutively assigned job number. In 1953, the system was altered somewhat to include the year and a job number (i.e., 63-4217). Thus instead of one sequence, the numbers begin anew with the new year. Although the sequence is largely chronological, the researcher should note that the job number was assigned at the time of development and some jobs that extended over a period of time or that were delayed in processing for any reason will not be filed in a strictly chronological manner.
  - 4 by 5 Negatives
    boxes 23-69; arranged by negative number
    - #4230 -- #5421, April 1949-May 1950 (Box 23)
    - #5427 -- #8406, May 1950-September 1951 (Box 24)
    - #8469 -- #10173, August 1951-May 1952 (Box 25)
    - #10208 -- #11704, June 1952-November 1952 (Box 26)
    - #11707 -- #13595, November 1952-May 1953 (Box 27)
    - #13607-18004 (Box 28)
    - 53-2 -- #53-387, May 1953-October 1953 (Box 28)
    - #53-388 -- #53-1072 (Box 29)
    - 54-4 -- #54-493, October 1953-February 1954 (Box 29)
    - #54-501 -- #541221, March 1954-June 1954 (Box 30)
    - #54-1223 -- #54-2488, June 1954-December 1954 (Box 31)
    - #54-2506 -- #55-894, December 1954-April 1955 (Box 32)
    - #55-903 -- #55-2193, April 1955-August 1955 (Box 33)
    - #55-2206 -- #55-3446, August 1955-December 1955 (Box 34)
    - #55-3450 -- #56-1140, December 1955-April 1956 (Box 35)
    - #56-1160 -- #56-2473, April 1956-July 1956 (Box 36)
    - #56-2507 -- #56-3767, July 1956-December 1956 (Box 37)
    - #56-3767 -- #57-794, December 1956-April 1957 (Box 38)
    - #57-797 -- #57-1758, March 1957-July 1957 (Box 39)
    - #57-1759 -- #57-2854, July 1957-January 1958 (Box 40)
    - #57-2855 -- #58-598, December 1957-April 1958 (Box 41)
    - #58-599 -- #58-1258, April 1958; July-September 1958 (Box 42)
    - #58-1263 -- #59-304, September 1958-March 1959 (Box 43)
    - #59-324 -- #59-1197, February 1959-July 1959 (Box 44)
    - #59-1198 -- #59-2004, July 1959-December 1959 (Box 45)
    - #59-2074 -- #60-1078, December 1959-June 1960 (Box 46)
    - #60-1084 -- #60-2230, June 1960-December 1960 (Box 47)
    - #60-2231 -- #61-1349, December 1960-June 1961 (Box 48)
    - #61-1350 -- #61-2493, June 1961-December 1961 (Box 49)
    - #61-2502 -- #62-796, December 1961-June 1962 (Box 50)
    - #62-1433 -- #63-547, August 1962-March 1963 (Box 51)
    - #63-549 -- #63-1958, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 52)
    - #63-1959 -- #64-966, October 1963-May 1964 (Box 53)
    - #64-978 -- #65-360, May 1964-February 1965 (Box 54)
    - #65-363 -- #65-2066, February 1965-August 1965 (Box 55)
    - #65-2068 -- #66-994, August 1965-April 1966 (Box 56)
    - #66-995 -- #66-3034, April 1966-October 1966 (Box 57)
    - #66-3052 -- #67-1242, October 1966-April 1967 (Box 58)
    - #67-1246 -- #68-244, April 1967-January 1968 (Box 59)
    - #68-253 -- #68-3844, January 1968-October 1968 (Box 60)
    - #68-3845 -- #69-1984, October 1968-June 1969 (Box 61)
    - #69-1988 -- #70-554, June 1969-February 1970 (Box 62)
    - #70-571 -- #70-3371, February-October 1970 (Box 63)
    - #70-3372 -- #70-2164, October 1970-July 1971 (Box 64)
    - #71-2175 -- #71-1243, July 1971-June 1972 (Box 65)
    - #72-1252 -- #73-647, June 1972-March 1973 (Box 66)
    - #73-663 -- #73-353, March 1973-November 1973 (Box 67)
    - #73-2354 -- #74-1395, October 1973-July 1974 (Box 68)
    - #74-1406 -- #75-1408, July 1974-April 1975 (Box 69)
  - 35 mm Negative Strips
    boxes 70-84
    - #75-1506 -- #75-2259, April 1975-September 1975 (Box 70)
    - #75-2260 -- #76-3154, September 1975-March 1976 (Box 71)
    - #76-3160 -- #76-3686, March 1976-September 1976 (Box 72)
    - #3691 -- #77-1241, September 1976-March 1977 (Box 73)
    - #77-1247-77-1815, March 1977-September 1977 (Box 74)
    - #77-1817 -- #78-2518, September 1977-May 1978 (Box 75)
    - #78-2521 -- #78-3130, May 1978-December 1978 (Box 76)
    - #78-3155 -- #79-3748, December 1978-June 1979 (Box 77)
    - #79-3750 -- #79-3998 (Box 78)
    - 79-1006 -- #79-1399, May 1979-December 1979 (Box 78)
    - #79-1409 -- #80-2996, December 1979-July 1980 (Box 79)
    - #80-3001 -- #81-3492, July 1980-February 1981 (Box 80)
    - #81-3501 -- #81-3994, January 1981-August 1981 (Box 81)
    - #81-1002 -- #82-1702, August 1981-August 1982 (Box 82)
    - #82-1714 -- #83-2193, May 1982-April 1983 (Box 83)
    - #83-2200 -- #83-2567, April 1983-December 1983 (Box 84)
  - 5 by 7 Negatives
    boxes 85-91
    - #101 -- #8052, February 1946-June 1951 (Box 85)
    - #51-8058 -- #56-3882, July 1951-December 1956 (Box 86)
    - #57-186 -- #59-1891, January 1957-October 1959 (Box 87)
    - #59-1891 -- #61-571, November 1959-March 1961 (Box 88)
    - #61-653 -- #63-2267, April 1961-December, 1963 (Box 89)
    - #63-2439 -- #67-2051, December 1963-July 1967 (Box 90)
    - #67-2108 -- #75-1244, July 1967-February 1975 (Box 91)
  - 8 by 10 Negatives
    - #101-2 -- #60-2263, February 1946-January 1960 (Box 92)
- Release forms (Box 93)
Subject Index to Prints and Transparencies
The index to photographic prints and transparencies (items located in boxes 1-22) was prepared by Bentley Historical Library archivists. The numbers cited refer to folder numbers which may contain one or more copy prints, contact prints or transparencies relating to the subject term.
Accidents -- 1, 146-147
Adult education -- 401
Advertisements -- 9, 502-503, 646-656 (See also Publicity)
Aerial views - Detroit -- 48
African Americans -- 243, 254, 407
Aged persons -- 525-526
Agriculture -- 11
Air conditioning unit -- 12
Air defense - DEW Line 13
Air pollution -- 253
Airports -- 178
Allen Park (Mich.) -- 158, 324
Ambassador Bridge -- 545
American Red Cross -- 522
American Telephone and Telegraph Company -- 22-25
Anchor Bay (Mich.) -- 160
Animals -- 18
Archives -- 553
Artificial larynx -- 19
Artificial satellites -- 544
Automobiles -- 30
Automobile industry -- 30, 296-297, 307, 568
Autumn -- 552
Bald, F. Clever -- 461
Baseball -- 593-596
Basketball -- 597
Battle Creek (Mich.) -- 322
Bay City (Mich.) -- 69, 103, 149, 669
Beauty contestants -- 379
Bell, Alexander Graham -- 34
Bell Telephone Laboratories -- 37
Bell Telephone Glee Club -- 310
Bell Telephone Hour -- 515, 642-643
Bellboy (paging system) -- 335
Birmingham (Mich.) -- 207
Blood donations -- 522
Blue Water Bridge (U.S.-Canada) -- 545, 547
Boats -- 42
Bowling -- 598
Boy Scouts -- 41, 283
Bridges - Michigan -- 43, 545, 547
Brittania (yacht) -- 42
Broadcasting -- 584, 596, 601
Building Services -- 44
Buildings -- 45-67
Buildings - Detroit -- 45-65
Buildings - Southfield -- 66
Business enterprises -- 616
Cable -- 68-80 Aerial -- 68 Breaks - Submarine -- 69-70 Bay City -- 69 Mackinaw City -- 70 St. Ignace -- 70 Buried -- 71-72 Coaxial -- 73 Construction -- 74 Submarine -- 78 Testing -- 79 Underground -- 80
Cadillac (Mich.) -- 569
Cadillac Building (Detroit, Mich.) -- 191
Cafeterias -- 44, 184
Calder, Alexander (Michigan Bell stabile) -- 62-63
Camping -- 84
Car phones -- 383-386
Cathode ray tube -- 88
Celebrations -- 293, 567, 569, 571-582, 583, 585, 588-589